KEVIN LE

IT COLLEGE GRADUATE

CONTACT

0432 333 800

businesskevinl360@gmail.com

Cairnlea 3023, VIC

SKILLS

- Physical Labour
- · Problem Solving
- Effective verbal and written communication
- Adaptable
- Experience in Trello
- Database Analysis:
 - o Database Management
 - Database Querying
 - o Database Manipulation

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology

RMIT University

FEBRUARY 2022 - NOVEMBER 2024

High School Diploma

Caroline Chisholm Catholic College

FEBRUARY 2016 - OCTOBER 2021

LANGUAGES

English

Vietnamese

PROFILE

An Information Technology graduate with a strong academic foundation in problem solving. Through my efforts in university and other relevant experiences, I have developed practical skills in configuring IT systems, managing databases, troubleshooting, and collaborating effectively in team settings. I hope that I can apply my knowledge and enthusiasm for technology towards you.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Student

RMIT University

FEBRUARY 2022 - NOVEMBER 2024

- Applied technical skills to create user-friendly documentation for IT processes and best practices.
- Learned and applied database applications through coursework, developing skills in querying, manipulating, and managing databases.

Capstone Project Member

VXHolohost Team, RMIT Univeristy

JULY 2024 - NOVEMBER 2024

- Designed and deployed the stakeholder-focused product utilising unfamiliar technologies and programming languages.
- Collaborated effectively with a diverse team to troubleshoot and resolve technical challenges.
- Developed documentation and delivered. presentations showcasing technical outcomes.

Event Staff

Simplified Projects

APRIL 2022 - CURRENT

- Occasional casual event staff member for an agency. This required me to take on many different roles, such as a labourer and busser.
- Adapted in unfamiliar settings, requiring quick adaptability to new environments as well as new colleagues.

Service Assistant

TGI Fridays

OCTOBER 2022- NOVEMBER 2023

- Delivered customer service by addressing their needs and resolving issues promptly.
- Perform multiple tasks in a high-paced restaurant environment.

KEVIN LE

IT COLLEGE GRADUATE

Liz Patterson ☐ 0424 473 657 ☐ liz.patterson@gmail.com

Holly Jones 0418 179 093 holly.jones@unimelb.edu.au

TESTIMONIALS

Liz Patterson

English Tutor & Freelance Writer

Soon after I started tutoring Kevin in 2020, he contracted COVID-19 and became seriously ill, missing over a month of school. With hard work, he made a full recovery. The whole time, he worked as hard as he could on his studies, never once making excuses, missing a tutoring session, or even arriving late. Ultimately, Kevin improved all key skills and did well in year 12 English. His tenacity, patience, and reliability would be an asset to any employer.

Holly Jones

Chemistry and Biology Tutor; Research Coordinator, University of Melbourne School of Population Health

Kevin is diligent, conscientious, and dedicated with a strong work ethic. As his tutor in Chemistry and Biology, I also noted strong technical aptitude. I have no hesitation recommending Kevin for any role where punctuality, reliability, and attention to detail are important.